<client>
<code>ilca579e162a5b0dc7c7d6e5532901801b2177ef909</code>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>606279778</number>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<secondhandListing>
<property>
<id>95141146</id>
<reference>V0004</reference>
<scope>1</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<postalcode>08002</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>La</streetName>
<streetNumber>88</streetNumber>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3819452</latitude>
<longitude>2.1730849</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="sale">
<price>13000</price>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[En venta dos plazas de parking con sistema automático de aparcamiento.
El nuevo sistema de parking robotizado en las Ramblas.
Dispone de vigilancia y seguridad total 24 horas.
La plaza es apta para vehículos con altura máxima 1,50m y dimensiones 5 x 2m.

Las dos plazas se venden por 25.000€, una plaza por 13.000€.

Ven a ver esta oportunidad de aparcamiento automatizado en la conocida Rambla de Barcelona.

¡Contáctanos para visitar este fabuloso parking!]]></comment>
<description>
<language>7</language>
<comment><![CDATA[A la venda dues places de pàrquing amb sistema automàtic d'aparcament.
El nou sistema de pàrquing robotitzat a les Rambles.
Disposa de vigilància i seguretat total 24 hores.
La plaça és apta per a vehicles amb alçada màxima 1,50m i dimensions 5 x 2m.

Totes dues places es venen per 25.000€, una plaça per 13.000 €.

Vine a veure aquesta oportunitat d'aparcament automatitzat a la coneguda Rambla de Barcelona.

Contacta'ns per visitar aquest fabulós pàrquing!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>5</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Vende-se dois lugares de parqueamento com sistema de parqueamento automático.
O novo sistema de estacionamento robótico em Las Ramblas.
Possui vigilância e segurança total 24 horas.
A praça é adequada para veículos com altura máxima de 1,50 me dimensões de 5 x 2 m.

Os dois assentos são vendidos por 25.€ 000, uma vaga para 13.000 €.

Venha e veja esta oportunidade de estacionamento automatizado na conhecida Rambla de Barcelona.

Contacte-nos para visitar este fabuloso parque de estacionamento!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Zu verkaufen zwei Parkplätze mit automatischem Parksystem.
Das neue automatisierte Parksystem auf Las Ramblas.
Es hat Überwachung und totale Sicherheit 24 Stunden.
Der Platz ist für Fahrzeuge mit einer maximalen Höhe von 1,50 m und einer Größe von 5 x 2 m geeignet.

Die beiden Sitze werden für 25 verkauft.000 €, ein Platz für 13.000 €.

Kommen Sie und sehen Sie sich diese automatisierte Parkmöglichkeit auf der bekannten Rambla in Barcelona an.

Kontaktieren Sie uns, um diesen fabelhaften Parkplatz zu besichtigen!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Vendesi due posti auto con sistema di parcheggio automatico.
Il nuovo sistema di parcheggio automatizzato sulle Ramblas.
Dispone di sorveglianza e sicurezza totale 24 ore.
La piazza è adatta a veicoli con un'altezza massima di 1,50 me dimensioni di 5 x 2 m.

I due posti sono venduti a 25.€000, un posto per 13.000 €.

Vieni a vedere questa opportunità di parcheggio automatizzato sulla famosa Rambla di Barcellona.

Contattaci per visitare questo favoloso parcheggio!]]></comment>
</description>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[For sale two parking spaces with automatic parking system.
The new robotic parking system on Las Ramblas.
It has surveillance and total security 24 hours.
The plaza is suitable for vehicles with a maximum height of 1.50m and dimensions 5 x 2m.

The two seats are sold for 25. € 000, one place for 13. € 000.

Come and see this automated parking opportunity on the well-known Rambla de Barcelona.

Contact us to visit this fabulous car park!]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/95141146]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>11</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/78/7b/10/907279744.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/c2/51/c2/907279733.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/16/ac/8f/907279743.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a5/7f/6f/907279745.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>6</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/13/7a/7b/907279759.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/0d/00/2e/907279742.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a3/2e/7e/907279741.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>6</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/fc/82/b7/907279734.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>11</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/12/3c/a2/907279746.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>11</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/8b/b5/68/907279750.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="garage">
<securityPersonnel>false</securityPersonnel>
<alarm>true</alarm>
<garageType>2</garageType>
<capacityMeters>12</capacityMeters>
<securityCams>true</securityCams>
<elevator>true</elevator>
<automaticDoor>true</automaticDoor>
</features>
</property>
<property>
<id>96423729</id>
<reference>V0010</reference>
<scope>1</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<floor>4</floor>
<postalcode>08001</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>dels Tallers</streetName>
<streetNumber>30</streetNumber>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3849768</latitude>
<longitude>2.1683091</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="sale">
<price>249000</price>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Precioso piso de 114m2 en la zona alta de Raval.

Se encuentra en una excelente localización, al lado de Plaza Catalunya y rodeado de bares y locales de tendencia.
La vivienda cuenta con un recibidor amplio, un salón-comedor muy amplio, cocina independiente con posibilidad de abrirla al salón, 3 dormitorios dobles donde uno de ellos dispone de balcón y además tiene dos baños para su comodidad.

La finca está en buen estado, rehabilitada hace menos de 5 años.
El ser una ultima planta, hace de este un piso que tenga mucha luminosidad.

¡Una oportunidad única para invertir obteniendo más de un 6,5% de rentabilidad!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>7</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Preciós pis de 114m2 a la zona alta de Raval.

Es troba en una localització excel·lent, al costat de Plaça Catalunya i envoltat de bars i locals de tendència.
L´habitatge compta amb un rebedor ampli, un saló-menjador molt ampli, cuina independent amb possibilitat d´obrir-la al saló, 3 dormitoris dobles on un d´ells disposa de balcó ia més té dos banys per a la seva comoditat.

La finca es troba en bon estat, rehabilitada fa menys de 5 anys.
Ser una ultima planta, fa d'aquest un pis que tingui molta lluminositat.

¡Una oportunitat única per invertir obtenint més d'un 6,5% de rendibilitat!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>8</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Красивая квартира 114м2 в верхней части Раваля.

Он находится в прекрасном месте, рядом с площадью Каталонии, в окружении модных баров и заведений.
В доме есть просторный холл, очень просторная гостиная-столовая, отдельная кухня с возможностью открытия ее в гостиную, 3 спальни с двуспальными кроватями, одна из которых имеет балкон, а также две ванные комнаты для вашего комфорта.

Ферма в хорошем состоянии, реабилитирована менее 5 лет назад.
Последний этаж делает квартиру очень светлой.

Уникальная возможность инвестировать с доходностью более 6,5%!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Bellissimo appartamento di 114m2 nella zona alta del Raval.

È in una posizione eccellente, vicino a Plaza Catalunya e circondato da bar e locali alla moda.
La casa ha un ampio ingresso, un soggiorno-pranzo molto spazioso, una cucina indipendente con la possibilità di aprirla sul soggiorno, 3 camere matrimoniali di cui una ha un balcone e dispone anche di due bagni per il vostro comfort.

L'agriturismo è in buone condizioni, riabilitato meno di 5 anni fa.
Essendo un ultimo piano, lo rende un appartamento molto luminoso.

Un'opportunità unica per investire ottenendo più del 6,5% di ritorno!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>DUTCH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Mooi appartement van 114m2 in het bovenste gedeelte van Raval.

Het ligt op een uitstekende locatie, naast Plaza Catalunya en wordt omgeven door trendy bars en uitgaansgelegenheden.
Het huis heeft een ruime hal, een zeer ruime woon-eetkamer, een aparte keuken met de mogelijkheid om deze te openen naar de woonkamer, 3 slaapkamers waarvan een met een balkon en ook twee badkamers voor uw comfort.

De boerderij is in goede staat, minder dan 5 jaar geleden gerehabiliteerd.
Omdat het een laatste verdieping is, is dit een appartement met veel licht.

Een unieke kans om te investeren met een rendement van meer dan 6,5%!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Schöne 114m2 Wohnung im oberen Bereich von Raval.

Es befindet sich in ausgezeichneter Lage neben der Plaza Catalunya und ist von trendigen Bars und Veranstaltungsorten umgeben.
Das Haus verfügt über eine geräumige Halle, ein sehr geräumiges Wohn-Esszimmer, eine separate Küche mit der Möglichkeit, sie zum Wohnzimmer zu öffnen, 3 Doppelzimmer, von denen eines einen Balkon hat, und zwei Badezimmer für Ihren Komfort.

Der Hof ist in gutem Zustand, vor weniger als 5 Jahren saniert.
Da es sich um eine letzte Etage handelt, ist dies eine Wohnung mit viel Licht.

Eine einzigartige Investitionsmöglichkeit mit einer Rendite von über 6,5 %!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Beautiful 114m2 apartment in the upper area of Raval.

It is in an excellent location, next to Plaza Catalunya and surrounded by trendy bars and venues.
The house has a spacious hall, a very spacious living-dining room, an independent kitchen with the possibility of opening it to the living room, 3 double bedrooms where one of them has a balcony and also has two bathrooms for your comfort.

The farm is in good condition, rehabilitated less than 5 years ago.
Being a last floor, makes this a flat that has a lot of light.

A unique opportunity to invest obtaining more than 6.5% return!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>3</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Bel appartement de 114m2 dans la partie supérieure du Raval.

Il bénéficie d'un excellent emplacement, à côté de la Plaza Catalunya et entouré de bars et de lieux branchés.
La maison dispose d'un hall spacieux, d'un salon-salle à manger très spacieux, d'une cuisine indépendante avec possibilité de l'ouvrir sur le salon, de 3 chambres doubles dont l'une d'elles possède un balcon et dispose également de deux salles de bain pour votre confort.

La ferme est en bon état, réhabilitée il y a moins de 5 ans.
Être un dernier étage, en fait un appartement très lumineux.

Une opportunité unique d'investir en obtenant plus de 6,5% de rendement !]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>9</language>
<comment><![CDATA[美丽的 114 平方米公寓位于拉瓦尔的上部。

地理位置优越，毗邻加泰罗尼亚广场，周围环绕着时尚的酒吧和场所。
房子有一个宽敞的大厅，一个非常宽敞的客厅餐厅，一个可以打开客厅的独立厨房，3 间双人卧室，其中一间带阳台，还有两间浴室，让您倍感舒适。

农场状况良好，不到 5 年前修复。
作为最后一层，这使它成为一个光线充足的公寓。

获得超过 6.5% 回报的独特投资机会！]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/96423729]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/92/d4/a8/946775647.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/3d/83/07/946775643.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/3f/01/f5/946775644.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d9/f2/c8/946775645.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/05/e2/1c/946775642.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/ea/e4/4f/946775551.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/33/25/aa/946775636.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/fe/62/b3/946775635.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/3e/5e/04/946775552.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/09/a4/f0/946775550.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/8c/38/7f/946775669.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/6e/5c/e4/946775556.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/77/1b/3b/946775554.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/2e/4b/38/946775646.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/b8/85/a4/946775549.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>14</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/40/bb/77/946775648.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a0/ca/c0/946775555.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>14</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/00/7e/ac/946775637.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/f9/32/66/946775553.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/4a/b3/31/946775649.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/eb/2b/b4/946775650.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="flat">
<constructedArea>114</constructedArea>
<bathrooms>2</bathrooms>
<buildingType>3</buildingType>
<bedrooms>3</bedrooms>
<furniture>0</furniture>
<conditionedAir>2</conditionedAir>
<orientation>false</orientation>
<energyCertification>
<rating>4</rating>
<performance>145.0</performance>
<emissionsRating>3</emissionsRating>
<emissionsValue>55.0</emissionsValue>
</energyCertification>
<elevator>false</elevator>
<windowsLocation>1</windowsLocation>
</features>
</property>
<property>
<id>96424240</id>
<reference>V0007</reference>
<scope>2</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<floor>2</floor>
<postalcode>08001</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>Joaquín Costa</streetName>
<streetNumber>46</streetNumber>
<door>4</door>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3829711</latitude>
<longitude>2.1655284</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="sale">
<price>215000</price>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnífico piso en la conocida calle de Joaquin Costa, cerca del teatre Goya y de Plaza Universitat.

Cuenta con una superficie de 71m2 donde encontramos un amplio salón luminoso, con balcón a la calle y suelos de parquet. También hay una cocina independiente, 3 dormitorios, de los cuales dos son dobles y exteriores y otro puede usarse como vestidor o cuarto de invitados. Además dispone de un baño completo con ducha.
Los techos con altos y con vigas a la vista. 
Toda la vivienda es amplia y luminosa, con una escalera en muy buen estado.

¡Ven a verlo y haz de este hogar tu lugar único!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>8</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Великолепная квартира на знаменитой улице Хоакина Коста, недалеко от театра Гойя и Университетской площади.

Он имеет площадь 71 м2, где мы находим большую светлую гостиную с балконом, выходящим на улицу, и паркетным полом.Также есть отдельная кухня, 3 спальни, две из которых двухместные и внешние, а еще одна может использоваться как гардеробная или комната для гостей.Также имеется полноценная ванная комната с душем.
Высокие потолки с открытыми балками.
Весь дом просторный и светлый, с лестницей в очень хорошем состоянии.

Приходите посмотреть и сделать этот дом своим уникальным местом!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>7</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnífic pis al conegut carrer de Joaquin Costa, a prop del teatre Goya i de Plaça Universitat.

Compte amb una superfície de 71m2 on trobem un ampli saló lluminós, amb balcó al carrer i terres de parquet.També hi ha una cuina independent, 3 dormitoris, dels quals dos són dobles i exteriors i un altre es pot fer servir com a vestidor o cambra de convidats.A més disposa d´un bany complet amb dutxa.
Els sostres amb alts i bigues a la vista.
Tota la vivenda és àmplia i lluminosa, amb una escala en molt bon estat.

Vine a veure'l i fes d'aquesta llar el teu lloc únic!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Prächtiges Apartment in der bekannten Straße Joaquin Costa, in der Nähe des Goya-Theaters und der Plaza Universitat.

Es hat eine Fläche von 71m2, wo wir ein großes, helles Wohnzimmer mit Balkon zur Straße und Parkettboden finden.Es gibt auch eine separate Küche, 3 Schlafzimmer, von denen zwei Doppel- und Außenzimmer sind und ein weiteres als Ankleidezimmer oder Gästezimmer genutzt werden kann.Es hat auch ein komplettes Badezimmer mit Dusche.
Hohe Decken mit sichtbaren Balken.
Das ganze Haus ist geräumig und hell, mit einer Treppe in sehr gutem Zustand.

Kommen Sie und sehen Sie es sich an und machen Sie dieses Zuhause zu Ihrem einzigartigen Ort!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnifico appartamento sulla famosa via Joaquin Costa, vicino al teatro Goya e Plaza Universitat.

Ha una superficie di 71m2 dove troviamo un ampio soggiorno luminoso, con balcone che si affaccia sulla strada e pavimenti in parquet.C'è anche una cucina indipendente, 3 camere da letto, di cui due doppie ed esterne e un'altra può essere utilizzata come spogliatoio o camera degli ospiti.Dispone inoltre di un bagno completo con doccia.
Soffitti alti con travi a vista.
L'intera casa è spaziosa e luminosa, con una scala in ottime condizioni.

Vieni a vederlo e fai di questa casa il tuo posto unico!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnificent apartment on the well-known Joaquin Costa street, near the Goya theater and Plaza Universitat.

It has an area of 71m2 where we find a large bright living room, with a balcony facing the street and parquet floors. There is also an independent kitchen, 3 bedrooms, of which two are double and exterior and another can be used as a dressing room or guest room. It also has a full bathroom with shower.
High ceilings with exposed beams.
The whole house is spacious and bright, with a staircase in very good condition.

Come see it and make this home your unique place!]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>SWEDISH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnifik lägenhet på den välkända Joaquin Costa-gatan, nära Goya-teatern och Plaza Universitat.

Den har en yta på 71m2 där vi hittar ett stort ljust vardagsrum, med balkong mot gatan och parkettgolv.Det finns också ett fristående kök, 3 sovrum, varav två är dubbelrum och exteriör och ett annat kan användas som omklädningsrum eller gästrum.Den har också ett komplett badrum med dusch.
Högt i tak med synliga takbjälkar.
Hela huset är rymligt och ljust, med en trappa i mycket gott skick.

Kom och se det och gör detta hem till din unika plats!]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/96424240]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/c6/37/36/946788584.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>11</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d2/d3/97/946788581.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>10</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/4c/a2/20/946788674.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/3e/36/2e/946788670.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>14</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/95/de/e1/946788582.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/bf/2b/b9/946788449.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/6c/7a/75/946788676.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/15/78/db/946788672.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/e3/3e/00/946788675.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/37/e9/9c/946788673.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/78/b3/6a/946788451.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/b1/68/94/946788450.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/28/82/45/946788446.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/0a/d5/57/946788668.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/92/68/c2/946788444.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>14</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/43/84/40/946788447.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/41/d8/b4/946788580.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/74/cf/39/946788442.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>11</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/68/60/b3/946788666.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/f0/89/3a/946788566.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/68/60/b3/946788443.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>14</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/91/52/a9/946788445.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>3</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/68/f9/f5/946788573.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/50/fa/c9/946788575.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/27/fc/c8/946788671.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/ae/65/68/946788669.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/db/1d/30/946788571.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/6b/29/92/946788572.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/53/fe/9d/946788574.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/87/1f/3c/946788667.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/dd/88/e5/946788448.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="flat">
<constructedArea>71</constructedArea>
<bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
<buildingType>3</buildingType>
<bedrooms>3</bedrooms>
<furniture>0</furniture>
<orientation>2</orientation>
<energyCertification>
<rating>4</rating>
<performance>145.0</performance>
</energyCertification>
<elevator>false</elevator>
<windowsLocation>1</windowsLocation>
</features>
</property>
<property>
<id>96424634</id>
<reference>V0013</reference>
<scope>1</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<floor>4</floor>
<postalcode>08003</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>dels Corders</streetName>
<streetNumber>11</streetNumber>
<door>2</door>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3856446</latitude>
<longitude>2.179596</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="sale">
<price>389000</price>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Estupendo piso en el corazón del carismático y bohemio barrio del Borne. 
Excelente orientación suroeste por lo tanto muy soleado y luminoso. Piso reformado con mucho gusto. 
La ubicación del piso es excelente, una calle paralela al mercado de S. Caterina y a dos pasos del museo Picasso. (Junto al metro Jaume I) 

Consta de un gran salón con cocina americana para poder disfrutar con la familia y amigos, 
dos habitaciones dobles muy luminosas, una con vestidor y un baño muy grande con bañera. 

Te invitamos a visitarlo y hacer de esta vivienda tu ÚNICO HOGAR.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>3</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Grand appartement au coeur du quartier charismatique et bohème d'El Borne.
Excellente orientation sud-ouest donc très ensoleillé et lumineux.Appartement rénové avec goût.
L'emplacement de l'appartement est excellent, une rue parallèle au S.Caterina et à deux pas du musée Picasso.(À côté du métro Jaume I)

Il se compose d'un grand séjour avec une kitchenette pour profiter en famille et entre amis,
deux chambres doubles très lumineuses dont une avec dressing et une très grande salle de bain avec baignoire.

Nous vous invitons à la visiter et à faire de cette maison votre SEULE MAISON.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Tolle Wohnung im Herzen des charismatischen und böhmischen Viertels El Borne.
Hervorragende Südwestausrichtung, daher sehr sonnig und hell. Geschmackvoll renovierte Wohnung.
Die Lage der Wohnung ist ausgezeichnet, eine Straße parallel zur S. Caterina und zwei Schritte vom Picasso-Museum entfernt. (Neben der U-Bahn Jaume I)

Es besteht aus einem großen Wohnzimmer mit Küchenzeile, um es mit Familie und Freunden zu genießen,
zwei sehr helle Doppelzimmer, eines davon mit Ankleidezimmer und ein sehr großes Badezimmer mit Badewanne.

Wir laden Sie ein, es zu besuchen und dieses Haus zu Ihrem EINZIGEN ZUHAUSE zu machen.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Grande appartamento nel cuore del quartiere carismatico e bohémien del Borne.
Ottimo orientamento sud-ovest quindi molto soleggiato e luminoso. Appartamento finemente ristrutturato.
La posizione dell'appartamento è ottima, una via parallela alla S. Caterina ea due passi dal museo Picasso. (Accanto alla metro Jaume I)

Si compone di un ampio soggiorno con angolo cottura da godere con la famiglia e gli amici,
due camere matrimoniali molto luminose di cui una con antibagno e un bagno molto ampio con vasca.

Vi invitiamo a visitarlo e fare di questa casa il vostro UNICO HOGAR.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>SWEDISH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Fantastisk lägenhet i hjärtat av den karismatiska och bohemiska stadsdelen El Borne.
Utmärkt sydvästlig orientering därför mycket soligt och ljust. Smakfullt renoverad lägenhet.
Lägenhetens läge är utmärkt, en gata parallell med S. Caterina och två steg från Picasso-museet. (Bredvid Jaume I-tunnelbanan)

Den består av ett stort vardagsrum med pentry att njuta av med familj och vänner,
två mycket ljusa dubbelrum, ett med omklädningsrum och ett mycket stort badrum med badkar.

Vi inbjuder dig att besöka det och göra detta hem till ditt ENDA HEM.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Great apartment in the heart of the charismatic and bohemian neighborhood of El Borne.
Excellent southwest orientation therefore very sunny and bright. Tastefully renovated apartment.
The location of the flat is excellent, a street parallel to the S. Caterina and two steps from the Picasso museum. (Next to the Jaume I metro)

It consists of a large living room with a kitchenette to enjoy with family and friends,
two very bright double rooms, one with a dressing room and a very large bathroom with a bathtub.

We invite you to visit it and make this home your ONLY HOME.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>7</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Fantàstic pis al cor del carismàtic i bohemi barri del Born.
Excel·lent orientació sud-oest per tant molt assolellat i lluminós. Pis reformat amb molt de gust.
La ubicació del pis és excel·lent, un carrer paral·lel al mercat de S. Caterina ia poca distància a peu del museu Picasso. (Al costat del metro Jaume I)

Consta d´un gran saló amb cuina americana per poder gaudir amb la família i amics,
dues habitacions dobles molt lluminoses, una amb vestidor i un bany molt gran amb banyera.

Et convidem a visitar-lo i fer d'aquest habitatge la teva ÚNIC LLAR.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>8</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Отличная квартира в самом сердце харизматичного и богемного района Эль Борн.
Отличная юго-западная ориентация, поэтому очень солнечно и ярко.Квартира со вкусом отремонтирована.
Расположение квартиры отличное, улица параллельна ул.Катерина и в двух шагах от музея Пикассо.(рядом с метро Жауме I)

Он состоит из большой гостиной с мини-кухней, где можно провести время с семьей и друзьями.
две очень светлые двухместные комнаты, одна с гардеробной и очень большая ванная комната с ванной.

Мы приглашаем вас посетить его и сделать этот дом вашим ЕДИНСТВЕННЫМ ДОМОМ.]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/96424634]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/71/a3/f0/946796421.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d2/fc/c4/946796433.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d2/35/96/946796447.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/4e/58/ca/946796419.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/b0/51/01/946796315.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/2f/e2/02/946796446.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/30/bf/4e/946796420.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/fe/7b/08/946796437.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/c2/a7/52/946796436.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/fb/ea/74/946796320.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/ed/60/1d/946796438.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/9f/ee/53/946796434.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/07/4e/a7/946796426.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/7f/9d/1a/946796321.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/b6/a7/bd/946796318.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/53/8b/f4/946796319.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/94/1e/ec/946796444.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/58/9e/ac/946796427.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>22</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d1/16/89/946796316.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/1c/8c/01/946796435.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/97/d5/24/946796445.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/e6/9a/ae/946796439.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/df/88/39/946796317.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/df/18/e0/946796428.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="flat">
<constructedArea>81</constructedArea>
<usableArea>63</usableArea>
<bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
<buildingType>3</buildingType>
<bedrooms>2</bedrooms>
<furniture>0</furniture>
<storageRoom>true</storageRoom>
<wardrobes>1</wardrobes>
<constructionYear>1884</constructionYear>
<conditionedAir>2</conditionedAir>
<orientation>false</orientation>
<energyCertification>
<rating>5</rating>
<performance>94.41</performance>
<emissionsRating>4</emissionsRating>
<emissionsValue>19.63</emissionsValue>
</energyCertification>
<elevator>true</elevator>
<windowsLocation>1</windowsLocation>
</features>
</property>
<property>
<id>96424975</id>
<reference>V0003</reference>
<scope>1</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<floor>3</floor>
<postalcode>08001</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>Nou de la Rambla</streetName>
<streetNumber>21</streetNumber>
<door>1</door>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3782693</latitude>
<longitude>2.1735967</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="sale">
<price>150000</price>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[PISO AL LADO DE RAMBLES Y PARKING EN VENTA

Apartamento de 64m2 al lado de Las Ramblas y del prestigioso Palau Güel. 
Dispone de un salón, una cocina independiente equipada al completo, un dormitorio doble, un baño con ducha, y además cuenta con un práctico trastero ideal para almacenaje.
Finca en correcto estado. 
Dispone de una plaza de parking en Las Ramblas para coche por 10mil euros.

Es una vivienda con muy buena rentabilidad para inversores.

¡Ven a verlo y aprovecha esta oportunidad única!
Puedes contactarnos por whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>3</language>
<comment><![CDATA[APPARTEMENT A PROXIMITE DES RANDONNEES ET PARKING A VENDRE

Appartement de 64m2 à côté de Las Ramblas et du prestigieux Palau Güel.
Il dispose d'un salon, d'une cuisine indépendante entièrement équipée, d'une chambre double, d'une salle de bain avec douche et d'un débarras pratique idéal pour le stockage.
Ferme en bon état.
Il dispose d'une place de parking sur Las Ramblas pour une voiture à 10 000 euros.

C'est une maison avec une très bonne rentabilité pour les investisseurs.

Venez le voir et profitez de cette opportunité unique!
Vous pouvez nous contacter par WhatsApp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>POLISH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[SPRZEDAM MIESZKANIE OBOK WĘDRÓWEK I PARKINGU

64m2 mieszkanie obok Las Ramblas i prestiżowego Palau Güel.
Posiada salon, w pełni wyposażoną niezależną kuchnię, dwuosobową sypialnię, łazienkę z prysznicem, a także praktyczny schowek idealny do przechowywania.
Gospodarstwo w dobrym stanie.
Ma miejsce parkingowe na Las Ramblas na samochód za 10 000 euro.

Jest to dom o bardzo dobrej rentowności dla inwestorów.

Przyjdź i skorzystaj z tej wyjątkowej okazji!
Możesz skontaktować się z nami przez WhatsApp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[APARTMENT NEXT TO RAMBLES AND PARKING FOR SALE

64m2 apartment next to Las Ramblas and the prestigious Palau Güel.
It has a living room with a balcony facing the street, a fully equipped independent kitchen, a double bedroom with a balcony, a bathroom with a shower, and it also has a practical storage room ideal for storage.
Farm in good condition.
It has a parking space on Las Ramblas for a large car for 20 thousand euros.

It is a house with very good profitability for investors.

Come see it and take advantage of this unique opportunity!
You can contact us by whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>8</language>
<comment><![CDATA[КВАРТИРА РЯДОМ С RAMBLES И ПАРКОВКОЙ НА ПРОДАЖУ

Квартира площадью 64 м2 рядом с бульваром Лас-Рамблас и престижным Палау Гуэль.
В нем есть гостиная, полностью оборудованная отдельная кухня, спальня с двуспальной кроватью, ванная комната с душем, а также практичная кладовая, идеально подходящая для хранения вещей.
Ферма в хорошем состоянии.
У него есть парковочное место на Las Ramblas для автомобиля за 10 000 евро.

Это дом с очень хорошей доходностью для инвесторов.

Приходите посмотреть и воспользоваться этой уникальной возможностью!
Вы можете связаться с нами по WhatsApp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[APPARTAMENTO VICINO A RAMBLES E PARCHEGGIO IN VENDITA

Appartamento di 64 m2 vicino a Las Ramblas e al prestigioso Palau Güel.
Ha un soggiorno, una cucina indipendente completamente attrezzata, una camera matrimoniale, un bagno con doccia, e dispone anche di un pratico ripostiglio ideale per riporre gli oggetti.
Fattoria in buone condizioni.
Dispone di un parcheggio sulle Ramblas per un'auto a 10.000 euro.

È una casa con un'ottima redditività per gli investitori.

Vieni a vederlo e approfitta di questa opportunità unica!
Puoi contattarci tramite whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[WOHNUNG NEBEN WANDERUNGEN UND PARKPLATZ ZU VERKAUFEN

64 m² großes Apartment neben Las Ramblas und dem prestigeträchtigen Palau Güel.
Es verfügt über ein Wohnzimmer, eine voll ausgestattete separate Küche, ein Schlafzimmer mit Doppelbett, ein Badezimmer mit Dusche und einen praktischen Abstellraum, der sich ideal zur Aufbewahrung eignet.
Bauernhof in gutem Zustand.
Es hat einen Parkplatz auf Las Ramblas für ein Auto für 10.000 Euro.

Es ist ein Haus mit sehr guter Rentabilität für Investoren.

Kommen Sie vorbei und nutzen Sie diese einmalige Gelegenheit!
Sie können uns per WhatsApp +34 606279778 kontaktieren.]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/96424975]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/8e/52/e9/946806824.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a9/75/84/946806565.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/15/d5/8e/946806826.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/5b/c1/27/946806567.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/47/a2/55/946806829.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/66/ae/2c/946806568.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/8c/ea/17/946806831.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/76/07/8f/946806566.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/aa/23/27/946806830.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/9d/6e/f1/946806569.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/dd/08/77/946806821.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a0/10/fb/946806838.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>14</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/53/55/cc/946806819.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/2a/67/22/946806837.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/bc/f4/fa/946806820.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/08/2e/ff/946806836.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/84/f5/53/946806832.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d6/12/50/946806815.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>3</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d2/1c/02/946806833.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a3/24/db/946806817.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/b5/23/7f/946806812.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/5f/14/8d/946806814.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/e3/88/28/946806564.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>3</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/63/07/24/946806813.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/16/95/dc/946806840.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/0b/12/3a/946806827.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="flat">
<constructedArea>64</constructedArea>
<bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
<buildingType>3</buildingType>
<bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
<furniture>0</furniture>
<parkingSpacesInPrice>true</parkingSpacesInPrice>
<orientation>false</orientation>
<energyCertification>
<rating>4</rating>
<performance>145.0</performance>
<emissionsRating>3</emissionsRating>
<emissionsValue>145.0</emissionsValue>
</energyCertification>
<elevator>false</elevator>
<windowsLocation>2</windowsLocation>
</features>
</property>
<property>
<id>96660124</id>
<reference>A0021</reference>
<scope>1</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<floor>1</floor>
<postalcode>08003</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>dels Banys Vells</streetName>
<streetNumber>14</streetNumber>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3842804</latitude>
<longitude>2.1809884</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="rent">
<price>900</price>
<depositType>2</depositType>
<depositMonths>2</depositMonths>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[LIBRE A PARTIR DE ABRIL - PISO DE TEMPORADA 

Piso ideal para parejas a dos pasos de la iglesia de Santa Maria del Mar en el corazón del Borne. 
Consta de una habitación doble con balcón exterior a calle, un salón con cocina americana el también con bacon exterior y Baño.

Piso de temporada (contrato de 11 meses) LIBRE A PARTIR DE ABRIL

¡Ven a verlo y aprovecha esta oportunidad única!
Puedes contactarnos por whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>POLISH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Idealny apartament dla par dwa kroki od kościoła Santa Maria del Mar w samym sercu Borne.
Składa się z pokoju dwuosobowego z zewnętrznym balkonem od strony ulicy, salonu z aneksem kuchennym, również z zewnętrznym balkonem, oraz łazienki.

Mieszkanie sezonowe (umowa na 11 miesięcy)

Przyjdź i skorzystaj z tej wyjątkowej okazji!
Możesz skontaktować się z nami przez WhatsApp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>5</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Apartamento ideal para casais a dois passos da igreja de Santa Maria del Mar no coração de Borne.
É composto por um quarto duplo com varanda exterior virada para a rua, uma sala com kitchenette, também com varanda exterior, e uma casa de banho.

Apartamento sazonal (contrato de 11 meses)

Venha conhecê-lo e aproveite esta oportunidade única!
Você pode entrar em contato conosco pelo whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>8</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Идеальная квартира для пар в двух шагах от церкви Санта-Мария-дель-Мар в самом сердце Борне.
Он состоит из спальни с двуспальной кроватью с внешним балконом, выходящим на улицу, гостиной с кухней, также с внешним балконом и ванной комнаты.

Сезонная квартира (договор на 11 месяцев)

Приходите посмотреть и воспользоваться этой уникальной возможностью!
Вы можете связаться с нами по WhatsApp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>7</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Pis ideal per parelles a dues passes de l'església de Santa Maria del Mar al cor del Born.
Consta d´una habitació doble amb balcó exterior a carrer, un saló amb cuina americana el també amb bacó exterior i bany.

Pis de temporada (contracte d'11 mesos)

Vine a veure'l i aprofita aquesta oportunitat única!
Pots contactar amb whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Appartamento ideale per coppie a due passi dalla chiesa di Santa Maria del Mar nel cuore del Borne.
Si compone di una camera matrimoniale con balcone esterno fronte strada, soggiorno con angolo cottura, anch'esso con balcone esterno, e bagno.

Appartamento stagionale (contratto 11 mesi)

Vieni a vederlo e approfitta di questa opportunità unica!
Puoi contattarci tramite whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Ideale Wohnung für Paare, nur wenige Schritte von der Kirche Santa Maria del Mar im Herzen von Borne entfernt.
Es besteht aus einem Doppelzimmer mit Außenbalkon zur Straßenseite, einem Wohnzimmer mit Kochnische, ebenfalls mit Außenbalkon, und einem Badezimmer.

Saisonwohnung (Vertrag 11 Monate)

Kommen Sie vorbei und nutzen Sie diese einmalige Gelegenheit!
Sie können uns per WhatsApp +34 606279778 kontaktieren.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>DUTCH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Ideaal appartement voor koppels op twee stappen van de kerk van Santa Maria del Mar in het hart van Borne.
Het bestaat uit een tweepersoonskamer met een buitenbalkon aan de straatkant, een woonkamer met een kitchenette, ook met een buitenbalkon, en een badkamer.

Seizoensappartement (11 maanden contract)

Kom kijken en profiteer van deze unieke kans!
U kunt contact met ons opnemen via whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>3</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Appartement idéal pour couple à deux pas de l'église de Santa Maria del Mar au coeur de Borne.
Il se compose d'une chambre double avec un balcon extérieur donnant sur la rue, d'un séjour avec coin cuisine, également avec un balcon extérieur, et d'une salle de bain.

Appartement saisonnier (contrat de 11 mois)

Venez le voir et profitez de cette opportunité unique!
Vous pouvez nous contacter par WhatsApp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Ideal apartment for couples two steps from the church of Santa Maria del Mar in the heart of Borne.
It consists of a double room with an exterior balcony facing the street, a living room with a kitchenette, also with an exterior balcony, and a bathroom.

Seasonal apartment (11-month contract)

Come see it and take advantage of this unique opportunity!
You can contact us by whatsapp +34 606279778.]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/96660124]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/da/13/cb/952918019.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d6/11/ee/952918115.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/1d/ac/e6/952918006.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/62/91/d1/952918007.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/08/01/fa/952918017.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/67/e0/76/952917926.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/88/c4/e7/952918107.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/83/e6/8c/952918108.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/86/48/36/952918116.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>10</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d3/c0/06/952918021.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/45/df/65/952917928.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/54/c5/9b/952918120.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/72/7e/83/952918023.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/73/b3/b5/952918022.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/fc/b4/11/952917930.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/34/8b/b6/952918109.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/96/11/6d/952918121.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/d0/ec/d1/952918125.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/f7/e6/93/952918123.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="flat">
<constructedArea>54</constructedArea>
<usableArea>36</usableArea>
<bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
<buildingType>3</buildingType>
<bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
<furniture>3</furniture>
<wardrobes>1</wardrobes>
<constructionYear>1840</constructionYear>
<orientation>false</orientation>
<energyCertification>
<rating>6</rating>
<performance>205.0</performance>
<emissionsRating>5</emissionsRating>
<emissionsValue>41.0</emissionsValue>
</energyCertification>
<elevator>false</elevator>
<windowsLocation>1</windowsLocation>
</features>
</property>
<property>
<id>96755637</id>
<reference>A0022</reference>
<scope>1</scope>
<address>
<visibility>2</visibility>
<country>es</country>
<floor>3</floor>
<postalcode>08003</postalcode>
<cityName>Barcelona</cityName>
<streetName>dels Banys Vells</streetName>
<streetNumber>14</streetNumber>
<door>4</door>
<coordinates>
<precision>1</precision>
<latitude>41.3842804</latitude>
<longitude>2.1809884</longitude>
</coordinates>
</address>
<contact>
<name>Único Hogar</name>
<email>info@unicohogar.com</email>
<preferredMethodType>1</preferredMethodType>
<phones>
<phone>
<number>930447902</number>
<redirection>true</redirection>
</phone>
</phones>
</contact>
<operation type="rent">
<price>1300</price>
<depositType>2</depositType>
<depositMonths>2</depositMonths>
</operation>
<descriptions>
<description>
<language>1</language>
<comment><![CDATA[PISO DE TEMPORADA EN EL CORAZÓN DEL BORNE A PARTIR DE JULIO MINIMO 3 MESES MAXIMO 11 MESES. 

Magnífico piso reformado en el corazón del Borne.
Cuenta con una superficie de 62m2 según catastro.

Dispone de un hermoso salón amplio y luminoso con característicos suelos de hidráulico y vigas de madera a la vista, tiene una cocina independiente equipada y con paredes de ladrillo a la vista. La vivienda cuenta con un dormitorio doble y un baño completo.
Toda la vivienda tiene acabados de calidad, con materiales originales y muy bien conservados.

Excelente ubicación, al lado de la Santa María del Mar, del conocido Paseo del Borne y a metros de la Barceloneta.

Te invitamos a visitarlo y hacer de esta vivienda tu ÚNICO HOGAR.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>5</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnífico apartamento renovado no coração de Borne.
Tem uma área de 62m2 conforme cadastro.

Tem uma bela sala espaçosa e luminosa com pisos hidráulicos característicos e vigas de madeira expostas, tem uma cozinha independente equipada com paredes de tijolos expostos. A casa tem um quarto duplo e uma casa de banho completa.
Toda a casa tem acabamentos de qualidade, com materiais originais e muito bem conservados.

Excelente localização, junto a Santa María del Mar, o conhecido Paseo del Borne e a poucos metros de Barceloneta.

Convidamo-lo a visitá-la e fazer desta casa a sua ÚNICA CASA.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>4</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Wunderschöne renovierte Wohnung im Herzen von Borne.
Es hat laut Kataster eine Fläche von 62m2.

Es verfügt über ein schönes, geräumiges und helles Wohnzimmer mit charakteristischen hydraulischen Böden und freiliegenden Holzbalken sowie eine separate Küche mit freiliegenden Ziegelwänden. Das Haus verfügt über ein Schlafzimmer mit Doppelbett und ein komplettes Badezimmer.
Das gesamte Haus ist hochwertig verarbeitet, mit Originalmaterialien und sehr gut erhalten.

Ausgezeichnete Lage, neben Santa María del Mar, dem bekannten Paseo del Borne und nur wenige Meter von Barceloneta entfernt.

Wir laden Sie ein, es zu besuchen und dieses Haus zu Ihrem EINZIGEN ZUHAUSE zu machen.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>6</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnifico appartamento ristrutturato nel cuore di El Borne.
Ha una superficie di 62m2 secondo catasto.

Dispone di un bel soggiorno ampio e luminoso con caratteristici solai idraulici e travi in legno a vista, ha una cucina indipendente dotata di pareti con mattoni a vista. La casa ha una camera matrimoniale e un bagno completo.
Tutta la casa ha finiture di pregio, con materiali originali e molto ben conservata.

Posizione eccellente, vicino a Santa María del Mar, al famoso Paseo del Borne ea pochi metri dalla Barceloneta.

Vi invitiamo a visitarlo ea fare di questa casa la vostra UNICA CASA.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>8</language>
<comment><![CDATA[СЕЗОННАЯ КВАРТИРА В ЦЕНТРЕ РОДИЛАСЬ С ИЮЛЯ МИНИМУМ 3 МЕСЯЦА МАКСИМУМ 11 МЕСЯЦЕВ.

Великолепная квартира с ремонтом в самом центре Борна.
По кадастру имеет площадь 62м2.

Он имеет красивую просторную и светлую гостиную с характерными гидравлическими полами и открытыми деревянными балками, а также отдельную кухню с кирпичными стенами.В доме есть спальня с двуспальной кроватью и полностью оборудованная ванная комната.
Весь дом имеет качественную отделку, оригинальные материалы и очень хорошо сохранились.

Отличное расположение, рядом с Санта-Мария-дель-Мар, знаменитым Пасео-дель-Борне и в нескольких метрах от Барселонеты.

Мы приглашаем вас посетить его и сделать этот дом вашим ЕДИНСТВЕННЫМ ДОМОМ.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>POLISH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Wspaniały odnowiony apartament w sercu El Borne.
Ma powierzchnię 62m2 wg katastru.

Posiada piękny przestronny i jasny salon z charakterystycznymi hydraulicznymi podłogami i odsłoniętymi drewnianymi belkami, posiada niezależną kuchnię wyposażoną w odsłonięte ceglane ściany. W domu znajduje się sypialnia dwuosobowa oraz łazienka z pełnym węzłem sanitarnym.
Cały dom ma wysokiej jakości wykończenia, oryginalne materiały i bardzo dobrze zachowane.

Doskonała lokalizacja, tuż obok Santa María del Mar, znanego Paseo del Borne i kilka metrów od Barcelonety.

Zapraszamy do odwiedzenia go i uczynienia z tego domu JEDYNEGO DOMU.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>SWEDISH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnifik renoverad lägenhet i hjärtat av El Borne.
Den har en yta på 62m2 enligt fastighetsregistret.

Den har ett vackert rymligt och ljust vardagsrum med karakteristiska hydrauliska golv och synliga träbjälkar, den har ett fristående kök utrustat med exponerade tegelväggar. Huset har ett sovrum med dubbelsäng och ett komplett badrum.
Hela huset har kvalitetsfinish, med originalmaterial och mycket välbevarat.

Utmärkt läge, bredvid Santa María del Mar, den välkända Paseo del Borne och några meter från Barceloneta.

Vi inbjuder dig att besöka det och göra detta hem till ditt ENDA HEM.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>DUTCH</language>
<comment><![CDATA[SEIZOENAPPARTEMENT IN HARTJE BORNE VANAF JULI MINIMAAL 3 MAANDEN MAXIMAAL 11 MAANDEN.

Schitterend gerenoveerd appartement in hartje Borne.
Het heeft een oppervlakte van 62m2 volgens het kadaster.

Het heeft een mooie ruime en lichte woonkamer met karakteristieke hydraulische vloeren en houten balken, het heeft een aparte keuken voorzien van bakstenen muren.Het huis heeft een tweepersoonsslaapkamer en een complete badkamer.
De gehele woning is hoogwaardig afgewerkt, met originele materialen en zeer goed bewaard gebleven.

Uitstekende locatie, naast Santa María del Mar, de bekende Paseo del Borne en een paar meter van Barceloneta.

Wij nodigen u uit om het te bezoeken en van dit huis uw ENIGE THUIS te maken.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>2</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnificent renovated apartment in the heart of El Borne.
It has an area of 62m2 according to cadastre.

It has a beautiful spacious and bright living room with characteristic hydraulic floors and exposed wooden beams, it has an independent kitchen equipped with exposed brick walls. The house has a double bedroom and a complete bathroom.
The whole house has quality finishes, with original materials and very well preserved.

Excellent location, next to Santa María del Mar, the well-known Paseo del Borne and meters from Barceloneta.

We invite you to visit it and make this home your ONLY HOME.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>3</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnifique appartement rénové au coeur d'El Borne.
Il a une superficie de 62m2 selon le cadastre.

Il dispose d'un beau salon spacieux et lumineux avec des sols hydrauliques caractéristiques et des poutres apparentes, il dispose d'une cuisine indépendante équipée de murs en briques apparentes. La maison a une chambre double et une salle de bain complète.
Toute la maison a des finitions de qualité, avec des matériaux d'origine et très bien conservés.

Excellent emplacement, à côté de Santa María del Mar, du célèbre Paseo del Borne et à quelques mètres de la Barceloneta.

Nous vous invitons à le visiter et à faire de cette maison votre SEULE MAISON.]]></comment>
</description>
<description>
<language>7</language>
<comment><![CDATA[Magnífic pis reformat al cor del Born.
Compte amb una superfície de 62m2 segons cadastre.

Disposa d´un bonic saló ampli i lluminós amb característics terres d´hidràulic i bigues de fusta a la vista, té una cuina independent equipada i amb parets de maó a la vista. L´habitatge compta amb un dormitori doble i un bany complet.
Tota la vivenda té acabats de qualitat, amb materials originals i molt ben conservats.

Ben situat, al costat de la Santa Maria del Mar, del conegut Passeig del Born ia metres de la Barceloneta.

Et convidem a visitar-lo i fer d'aquest habitatge la teva ÚNIC LLAR.]]></comment>
</description>
</descriptions>
<links>
<link>
<language>1</language>
<url><![CDATA[https://www.idealista.com/inmueble/96755637]]></url>
</link>
</links>
<images>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/9e/b9/65/938083648.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/e4/5c/67/938083650.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/47/43/4d/938083633.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/1c/b0/ed/938083646.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>9</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/32/4e/83/938083647.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/11/8a/62/938083631.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>2</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/4a/6d/14/938083632.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/81/9b/92/938083644.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/a4/b5/ac/938083645.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>0</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/98/d5/ec/938083643.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/1f/1f/21/938083642.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/11/34/8b/938083641.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/70/4c/32/938083527.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>4</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/03/b1/6a/938083625.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/4b/48/5d/938083528.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/bd/f4/0b/938083649.jpg]]></url>
</image>
<image>
<code>1</code>
<url><![CDATA[https://img3.idealista.com/blur/DATAFEED/0/id.pro.es.image.master/f0/f6/5d/938083651.jpg]]></url>
</image>
</images>
<features type="flat">
<constructedArea>65</constructedArea>
<usableArea>55</usableArea>
<bathrooms>1</bathrooms>
<buildingType>3</buildingType>
<bedrooms>1</bedrooms>
<furniture>3</furniture>
<conditionedAir>2</conditionedAir>
<orientation>false</orientation>
<energyCertification>
<rating>4</rating>
<performance>145.0</performance>
<emissionsRating>3</emissionsRating>
<emissionsValue>55.0</emissionsValue>
</energyCertification>
<elevator>false</elevator>
<windowsLocation>1</windowsLocation>
</features>
</property>
</secondhandListing>
</client>
